Finding Aid for the Sidney Reznick Papers PASC.0297
UCLA Library Special Collections
Sidney Reznick papers
1939-1990
1947-1968
UCLA Library Special Collections
Reznick, Sidney
PASC.0297
37.2 linear feet (92 boxes and 1 microfilm box)
Sidney Reznick worked as comedy writer in radio and television. The collection consists of scripts related to his career, mostly for the Garry Moore television show (1958-1961), as well as sound recordings. A 2013 addition contains project files, bound volumes of scripts, photographs, and radio transcription discs.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED MICROFILM MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mr. Sidney Reznick, 1999. Additional materials gift of Bruce and Robert Reznick, 2013.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9956346353606533
Biographical Note
Sidney Reznick was born in Manhattan on July 29, 1919. He started writing comedy in high school. He attended the CCNY School of Business and graduated in 1941. Starting in the 1940s he wrote for radio, and later television. Reznick worked with the likes of Jimmy Durante, Jack Paar, and Bob Hope, and was a staff writer for Johnny Carson on The Tonight Show. In 1957, he reated the comedy game show Sez Who? Reznick died in Los Angeles in 2012.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of comedy writer Sidney Reznick. The bulk of the collection includes complete scripts and a small number of partial scripts from the Garry Moore Show television program. A small number of the scripts are annotated and/or may include production information. Also included is a small amount of microfilm negatives containing unidentified scripts from the Alan Young show, Meet Your Match, and the Jackie Gleason Show. Additionally, there is a published copy of Reznick's book, How to Write Jokes (circa 1954) and what appears to be commercially produced sound recordings featuring Burns and Allen, Edgar Bergen and Charlie McCarthy, Fiber McGee and Molly, and Ed "Archie" Gardner, and musical performer Gertrude Lawrence. A 2013 addition contains project files, bound volumes of scripts, and radio transcription discs. Also included in this collection are photographs.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Series 1. Scripts, project files, and printed materials
Series 2. Sound recordings
Series 3: Photographs
- Series 1: Scripts, project files, and printed materials, 1939-1990
  Scope and Contents
  The bulk of the series consists of script material for the Garry Moore Show television program. Included are what appear to be completed scripts and a small amount of partial scripts. A small number of the scripts are annotated and/or may include production information. Also included are a small number of microfilm negatives containing unidentified scripts from the Alan Young show, Meet your match, and the Jackie Gleason show and the Wrigley show.
  Arrangement
  Materials from the original accession are organized alphabetically. Materials from the 2013 addittion reflect the existing order in which they were received from the donor.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED MICROFILM MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Garry Moore Show - script and run down, 1958 Dec 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1958 Dec 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    This is the Christmas Show episode.
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1958 Dec 30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1959 Jan 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Includes guest stars Rudy Vallee, Milt Kames, and Benny Goodman.
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information, 1959 Jan 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information, 1959 Jan 27 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information, 1959 Feb 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information, 1959 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information, 1959 Feb 17 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information, 1959 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information, 1959 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production information - revision 1, 1959 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and run down, 1959 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and run down, 1959 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script - revision 1, 1959 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and run down - revision 1, 1959 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1959 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1959 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1959 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Guest stars include Ed Wyn, Kaye Ballard, and Johnny Desmond.
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1959 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and run down, 1959 Sept 29 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and run down, 1959 Oct 13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and rundown - revision 1, 1959 Oct 20 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1959 Nov 3 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1959 Nov 3 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1959 Nov 10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1959 Nov 24 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1959 Dec 8 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1959 Dec 29 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 Jan 5 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 Jan 12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 Jan 19 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and rundown, 1960 Jan 26 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 Feb 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 Feb 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 Feb 16 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and rundown, 1960 Feb 16 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 Feb 23 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 March 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 March 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 March 8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete, annotated script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 March 29 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and production staff list, 1960 March 29 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script - revision 1, 1960 March 29 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 April 5 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and rundown - revision 1, 1960 April 5 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1960 April 12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script, 1960 April 19 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 April 26 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 April 26 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 May 10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1960 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production staff list - revision 1, 1960 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1960 May 31 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 May 31 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 June 14 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 June 21 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown, 1960 June 28 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script, 1960 Sept 27 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script and production staff list, 1960 Sept 27 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 Oct 4 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete, annotated script and rundown, 1960 Oct 4 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 Oct 11 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1960 Oct 11 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script and rundown, 1960 Oct 18 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and production staff list, 1960 Oct 25 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1960 Oct 25 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1960 Nov 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1960 Nov 15 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script, 1960 Nov 15 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 Nov 15 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1960 Nov 22 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 Nov 29 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script and rundown, 1960 Dec 6 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 Dec 20 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1960 Dec 20 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated incomplete script, 1960 Dec 20 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1960 Dec 27 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 Jan 3 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 Jan 3 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1961 Jan 10 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 Jan 10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 Jan 17 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 Jan 17 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1961 Jan 24 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1961 Jan 31 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1961 Feb 7 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1961 Feb 14 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script, 1961 Feb 21 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 Feb 28 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 March 7 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script - revision 1, 1961 March 7 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 March 14 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 April 4 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 April 18 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated incomplete script, 1961 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated script - revision 1, 1961 May 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 May 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - annotated incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script, 1961 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 May 30 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 May 30 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, 1961 June 6 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script and rundown - revision 1, 1961 June 13 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 June 27 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 June 27 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Garry Moore Show - script and rundown - revision 1, 1961 Oct 24 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script - revision 1, 1961 Oct 24 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Garry Moore Show - script - revision 1, 1961 Nov 21 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Garry Moore Show - incomplete script and production staff list - revision 1, 1961 Nov 21 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Garry Moore Show - script material, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Garry Moore Show - script, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Alan Young Show microfilm negative, 1946 (Box 10)
  - Assorted radio comedy microfilm negative, 1946 (Box 10)
  - Jackie Gleason Show microfilm negative, 1963-1965 (Box 10)
    Includes Neutral backgrounds, The Poor Soul, Reggie, Rum Dum.
  - Meet Your Match microfilm negative, undated (Box 10)
  - Wrigley Show microfilm negative, undated (Box 10)
  - Orben's Current Comedy vol. 2 no.1 through vol. 4 no. 2, 1959 November-1961 December (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Orben's Current Comedy vol. 4 no.1 through vol. 4 no. 12, 1962 January - October (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Orben's Current Comedy vol. 1, 2, 6, 7, 8, 1958 November, 1959 November, 1963 November, 1964 November, 1965 November (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - How to Write Jokes, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    6 copies
  - The Gag Recap, 1963 October, 1963 December, 1964 February-July, 1964 Spetember, 1965 January (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fun Master vol. 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Fun Master vol. 2, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Fun Master Monthly "The Comedian" vol. 10 no.6 114th issue through vol. 10 no.11 issue 119, 1960 January (February) - June (July) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Fun Master Monthly "The Comedian" vol. 11 no.1 through vol. 11 no.9, 1960 August (September) - 1961 April (May) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Fun Master Monthly "The Comedian" vol. 11 no.10 through vol. 12 no. 5, 1961 April (May) - 1960 August (January) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Fun Master Monthly "The Comedian" vol. 12 no. 6, 1962 January - February (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Original Radio and Television Properties vol. 2, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Accident to Business, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Homes to Life, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Children to Entertainment World, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Polly Bergen Show, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Europe to Holidays, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Sketches vol. 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Love to Music, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The Recap vol. 5, 1959 January - December (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Names to Sleep, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The Recap vol. 8, 1962 January - December (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Society to Western, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Songs for Sale Jan Murray Monologues and Guest Spots, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Sketches vol. 1, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Back that Fact Starring Joey Adams, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Jack Paar Show, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Comedy Surgeons and Situations, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show: Two Person Routines, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The Recap vol. 4, 1958 January - December (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Jack Paar Show: Two Person Routines vol. 1, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The Recap vol. 7, 1961 January - December (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jack Paar Show: Two Person Routines vol. 2, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jack Paar Show: Cast Routines vol. 1, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Jack Paar Show: Cast Routines vol. 2, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Jack Paar Show: Take-Offs on TV shows vol. 1, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Jack Paar Show: Take-Offs on TV shows vol. 2, 1955 August 16 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Gary Moore Show: Sketches vol. 2, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Gary Moore Show: Routines, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Borden Show Starring Ed Wynn, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Jack Paar Show: Monologues vol. 1, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Jack Paar Show: One Person Routines vol. 3, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Jack Paar Show: Monologues vol. 2, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Jack Paar Show: One Person Routines vol. 1, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Water damaged
  - Jack Paar Show: One Person Routines vol. 4, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Jack Paar Show: One Person Routines vol. 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Jack Paar Show: Translation Routines, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Jack Paar Show: Louis Nye Routines, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Songs for Sale Starring Steve Allen Contestants In Reviews, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Songs for Sale Starring Jan Murray Contestants In Reviews vol. 1, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Songs for Sale Starring Jan Murray Contestants In Reviews vol. 2, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Songs for Sale Starring Jan Murray Contestants In Reviews vol. 3, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - The Sam Stevenson Show, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Gary Moore Show Sketches vol. 1, 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Great Talent Hunt, 1948-1951 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Scripts Doctor to Fortune Teller, 1944-1947 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Ethel Merman Show, 1949- (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Contemporary Comedians vol. 1, 1938-1942 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show: The People Speak, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Contemporary Comedians vol. 2, 1939-1944 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Scripts College to Crime, 1940-1946 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Scripts Accidents to Clothes, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show: The People Speak vol. 2, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Scripts Married Life to Restaurants, 1942-1949 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show: Sketches vol. 1, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: School to Western, 1943-1949 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show: Sketches vol. 2, 1956-1957- (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Television Material, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show: Two Person Routines Regular Cast Members vol. 1, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: History to Love, 1939-1946 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: General Material, 1940-1950 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Continuity, 1942-1946 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Monologue, 1941-1945 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Routines and Blackouts, 1943-1949 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show: Two Person Routines Regular Cast Members vol. 2, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia of Contemporary Humor: Sketches and Blackouts, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Blind Date Starring Jan Murray, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Meet Your Match Starring Jan Murray, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Alan Young TV Scripts, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Bob Musel Stuff, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Bob Hope, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Camel Program, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Ethel Merman Show, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Gag Recap, Nov 1954, 1955, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Gag Recap, 1960, 1963, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - How to Write Comedy and Humor, 1964, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Damone - First Draft, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Dean Martin Show, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Henry Youngman - Great Talent Hunt, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Jack Parr Bits, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - What You Would Have Said, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Thought For the Day, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Love American Style, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Gary Moore Show, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Gary Moore Show, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Johnny Carson Show Sketches, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Martin and Lewis Show, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Odd Couple, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Milton Berle Show, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Phil Selvers Show, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Polly Bergen Show, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Polly Bergen Show, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Polly Bergen Show, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Polly Bergen Show - Bob Hope (Guest), undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Rod Skelton Show, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - "Three's Company", undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Rango, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Robert Q Lewis Show, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Victor Borge (Material Handed In), undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - "Three on a Honeymoon", undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - "Jackie Gleason Show Syndication", undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - My Boy Shirley, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Jackie Gleason Show Residuals, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - JG Blackouts, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - JG Blackouts, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Jackie Gleason Show Blackouts, 1963-1964 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - JG Blackouts, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - JG Blackouts, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - JG Blackouts, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - JG Blackouts, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Jackie Gleason Show, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Jackie Gleason Show Premises and Ideas, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Jackie Gleason Show Miscellaneous Ideas, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Jackie Gleason Monologue - "The Ray Bloch Story", undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Jackie Gleason Monologue - "The Ray Bloch Story", undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Charlie Bratton (Premises), undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Charlie Bratton ("The Lord Mouth"), undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Charlie Bratton ("Charlie's Hair Treatment"), undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - The Lord Mouth ("Charlie's Hair Treatment"), undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Fenwick Babbitt, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Fenwick Babbitt, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Fenwick Babbitt - Bank Stuff, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Mother Fletcher ("Round the World Travel Kit"), undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Mother Fletcher (Items), undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Mother Fletcher (Story), undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Poor Soul "Friendship Club", undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Poor Soul "Camping Out", undated (Box 50, Folder 17)